beautymnl.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy

Taste Central Curators Inc. (“BeautyMNL”, “we”, “us”, “our”) respects the privacy of our Users (“you”, “your”, “yours”, “Users”). Please read on to learn what information we collect from you and how we use that information. By using or accessing www.beautymnl.com (the “Service”), you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by all the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

  * What information does BeautyMNL collect?
  * Will BeautyMNL share information it collects?
  * Is Personal Information About Me Secure?
  * What Choices Do I Have?
  * Contact Us

We collect various types of personal information from our Users. Personal information refers to information by which you can be identified. We may use this information to, among other things, personalize and improve our services, allow our users to register as a member, contact Users, fulfill your order requests for products, analyze how Users use the Service, or as otherwise indicated in this Privacy policy. We may share certain types of Personal Information with third parties. We collect the following types of information: 

  * We receive and store any information you knowingly provide us. We collect Personal Information such as your name, username, email address, mobile phone number, shipping address and the email addresses of your friends (which BeautyMNL will use only for the purposes of inviting your friends to use the Service). We may also collect your shopping behavior and preferences, and maintain a record of the purchases and transactions you make on our web site. If you register as a member using your Facebook account, you understand that some of your information may be transmitted into your BeautyMNL account from your Facebook account. 

  * Non-Personal Information is defined as information that does not identify a specific User. As is true for most web sites, we automatically receive and record information on our server log files from your browser including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), URLs that refer visitors to the web site, operating system, general geographic location, date and time stamp and cookie information. 
  * A “cookie” is a small text file stored on a User’s computer or other Internet-connected device which contains information about the User. We use cookies to save you time while browsing and shopping on BeautyMNL and help us better understand shopping behavior, with the purpose of providing a customized shopping experience. Cookies also tell us which pages in our web site people have visited and by how many people. We also collect information by use of “web beacons,” also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, to track your use of our web site pages and promotions, or we may allow third party service providers to use these on our behalf. Web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certain pages on our web site or emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. We may also use third-party website analytics tools (such as Google) to collect information. BeautyMNL treats information collected by cookies, web beacons and third-party website analytics tools as Non-Personal information. 

We will not rent, sell nor disclose your Personal Information with other parties except only as described below: 

  * Some circumstances call for us to share some of your Personal Information with BeautyMNL merchants. For example, we may share with BeautyMNL merchants information to fulfill your orders as well as aid in post-purchase requests like responding to your questions and comments and facilitating returns and exchanges. This means that a BeautyMNL merchant may communicate with you directly should they choose to do so. We specifically disclaim any responsibility or liability for the actions of such BeautyMNL merchant. 

  * We employ other companies as authorized third party providers to perform a function or provide services for you on our behalf. For example, a third party service provider may send out or distribute transactional and promotional emails. We may also share Personal Information to third party service providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal mail or electronic mail, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the Website, troubleshot and provide customer service. We will only share your Personal Information to the extent that we deem it necessary or related to such transaction or service. The use of Personal Information by such parties is governed by their privacy policies and is not subject to our control. 

  * Remarketing is a way for us to reconnect with our Users. Third-party marketing vendors may be enlisted by BeautyMNL to provide remarketing services, and may display ads of BeautyMNL on sites across the Internet. Third-party marketing vendors use cookies to serve ads based on your past visits to BeautyMNL’s web site. 

  * We may transfer Personal Information about our Users in the event we sell, merge or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Personal Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. 

  * We reserve the right to release Personal Information about you if we are required to do so by law; in compliance with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process; to enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, our Website Terms and Conditions or other agreements; or if we deem it necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of BeautyMNL, our employees, our Users, or others. We may disclose information to companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

BeautyMNL takes extra measures to protect the security of your Personal Information. You can access your Personal Information on our web site through your account, which is protected by a password. This password is encrypted. To keep your Personal Information secure, we recommend that you do not share your password with any individual. If you registered for an account via Facebook, you may have additional or different sign-in protections through Facebook. 

Additional measures are in place to ensure the security of your Personal Information. Your Personal Information is stored on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. We encrypt certain sensitive information, such as credit card information, using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your Personal Information is safe as it is transmitted to us. 

We strive to protect the privacy of our Users and their Personal Information, but no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot guarantee the complete security of information transmitted to or from our web site, and are not responsible for the actions of third parties that may receive such information. 

You can always opt not to disclose information to us. Please take note, however, that we require some information for you to engage in some activities and access certain features on the web site. We will send you emails related to your transaction (“Transactional Emails”). You cannot opt out of Transactional Emails. We will also send you emails in conjunction with our products and promotional offers (“Promotional Emails”). You can opt out of Promotional Emails by changing your account settings, clicking on the Unsubscribe button contained in the email or sending an email to [sos@beautymnl.com.](mailto:sos@beautymnl.com)

Got questions? You’ll find answers in our FAQs page. If you want to reach out (or just want to say hey), feel free to [email us.](mailto:sos@beautymnl.com)
